- Good morning.
Reginald? What would you
like me to call you?
Reggie is fine.
Okay, Reggie, tell me more about yourself.
Ever since I was young,
I always dreamed of being a rockstar.
Guys… guys we're next.
Okay, let's pray first.
Okay, let's pray.
Lord God.
Thank you for the gift of music,
and thank you for the opportunity to play.
We wish for a smooth performance.
Guide our hands and our hearts, Lord,
as we play, together.
And may our talents bring you glory, God.
This we ask through your Son,
Jesus Christ--
Let's go! Let's go!
- Let's go! Let's rock!
- Let's go!
Amen.
Let's go!
You changed too quickly
It was a little before May when you left
And then you were gone
That's my band
Sinagtala.
It was a different time,
a different world.
So much has happened.
You said your promises
Would never be broken
The love that you've taken away
A promise you'll never break
Are now just worthless words
Words I should never have believed
From the break of dawn
To the fall of night
Dreaming of you beside me
And I don't want to wake up
Until you tell me
Where you've gone
Where are you?
From the break of dawn
To the fall of night
Dreaming of you beside me
And I don't want to wake up
Until you tell me
Where you've gone
Where are you?
- Hi, Nanny.
- Hey.
You've got to drink this up.
Okay.
Thank you.
Need anything?
- What about a shot?
- You're delusional.
I've got to go, I have editing work.
Oh, my nanny's going places.
Of course.
You didn't pay for my film school
just for me to slack off.
And look!
- The baby prime just arrived!
- Wow!
- Big time!
- Big time! You bet.
- Thanks again, Yaya.
- You're welcome, my dear.
I got drunk and then…
I crashed.
So, I went to jail.
And when I got out, I couldn't get a job.
That was when
my daughter's mom left me.
I still had to earn enough for support.
For Mikey, my daughter.
So I thought I should start a business.
"Beautiful Beautiful" by Sinagtala.
Sir?
Could you turn that up?
It's my favorite song.
Thank you.
Are you a fan?
Of course!
It's a shame they've disbanded.
Yes.
The lead vocalist killed himself.
What?
June?
Is that you?
Yes?
You can't smoke in here.
It's my last day, don't worry.
Are you okay?
Yes, it's nothing.
I'm adopted.
My real parents,
they gave me away.
Nobody knew why.
The ones who raised me,
I don't really think that…
they care about me.
Where to, Ma'am?
Home, please.
But Daboy, do me a favor.
Could you not mention
any of this to my father?
Not mention what?
Dad.
You're here.
So,
you got fired, again?
Yes, Dad.
Did you fight with your bosses again?
I did but I was only doing my job, Dad!
His ideas and plans were all wrong
for the company!
Which one of you was the boss?
He was.
See?
Then he's never wrong!
You're too smart for your own good.
You'll never find a job at this rate!
Damn that referee,
we're close to just one point--
Oh, hand me those glasses.
We're just out of luck, Boss.
Hey, what are you doing?
- Oh, Dad.
- What are you doing?
Oh, I was just--
Into the song, that's all.
This my favorite girl group, see?
Aren't they cute?
- Which one's your type?
- Oh, they are pretty.
I like the one with red hair.
The red one? See? He's my son all right!
- He gets his good taste from me!
- You think?
Here, kid…
Have a shot.
So, Dad, my dudes…
How was the game?
Well, it was a tie.
They won the first game.
We lost the second!
We were never going to win.
They had this prodigy from LaSalle.
No, we could have won that.
If you had come along
we could have had a shooter.
Yes!
Don't worry, we'll get them next time.
Oh, and after this go get ready.
You're coming with us.
Where?
But I've got my exams.
Exams?
Son…
You're so good you could
do them with your eyes closed!
You didn't even come to the game.
Come on, Son.
Spend some quality time with me.
Boss, school is important.
Just let the kid be and let's go.
My kid doesn't need to study.
He's the smartest one there is!
He gets his basketball skills from me.
And his smarts from his mom.
And that's why she left me.
That wasn't just smart,
that was ingenious!
Right, right.
What about the moves with women, Boss?
As for women,
we approach them differently.
I'm kind of a barbarian.
But this one's a smooth gentleman.
So, we'll need you, kid.
We're going out for women.
A wingman!
But, why?
Son, let me tell you how this works.
You'll be the bait.
And when a girl finds you attractive,
she'll come along.
While we get to know her lady friends.
That's what you call teamwork!
- Exactly!
- Cheers, to our success.
Cheers!
I'm gay.
And I don't know how to tell my father.
But I don't even fool around.
It's just hard to go along with
everything my macho dad does.
Money's been hard lately.
Yes…
I don't like having to
act like this tequila isn't trash.
Shut up.
Somebody might hear you! I need this job.
Cheers, then.
Cheers.
- This one's pretty good.
- I know, right?
- Do you still have to work?
- Nope. I'm done.
Hide me.
- What?
- What's happening?
Why are you hiding?
That--
- That guy can't know I work here.
- What?
- Which one?
- That one. Would you talk to him?
- That big guy over there.
- The one in the jacket?
Yes! That one!
- I see him now.
- Fine, don't worry.
He can't know.
Find some place to hide.
Go, while he's not looking.
- Megan?
- Yes?
Why are you hiding from him?
I'll be over there.
Go, go.
Hi, I'm Camille.
- Hi, Camille, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm ashamed to admit that…
I'm a prostitute.
These days…
women have it hard.
Hello!
So, how are you guys?
And why are you up so late?
Me?
I just stopped to eat.
You know, I have to stay on the road.
I'm a driver now so…
Don't be dramatic.
At least you still have a job.
Oh?
Gave it to your boss again, huh?
You're still stubborn.
You haven't changed.
Hey, Ju--
Shut up, June.
You're rich. You never needed to work.
That's not true.
Dad is giving me a hard time.
What about my Dad?
He makes me go out with him
on the night before my exams!
Oh, you're all lucky.
Stop complaining.
Being a dad is tough, you know.
So, how's your baby, Reg?
Still there.
With her crazy mom.
Wow, that's a little bitter.
You're still in love, aren't you?
I'm not bitter at all.
I've moved on. Ages ago.
Dude…
Why are you driving a cab?
It's just my little sideline.
I'm still appying for jobs in corporate.
But, it's hard.
At least for ex-cons.
You know, the other day…
I had this passenger who
heard one of our songs.
And she told me, that we disbanded
because the lead vocalist killed himself.
So, you're an urban legend now, Reggie.
Wait, our songs still play on the radio?
I know, right?
How is Pao?
Why isn't she on the call with us?
I haven't had any news from Laguna.
You know, Pao.
She's never on social media.
I hope she's okay.
I miss her.
Why don't we go in person?
Laguna isn't that far.
Yes!
We could go next week.
Okay.
Sure.
Is that you, Daddy?
Yes, baby.
Didn't I tell you Daddy was a singer?
A rockstar!
Look, that's my band!
Amazing!
Did you like the song?
That was fun.
I had so much fun!
Thanks for taking me shopping.
No, sorry. Not right now.
Baby, Mommy's here.
- Hi, Mommy!
- Hey, baby.
Hi, Uncle Billy!
The enrollment is next week.
Quarterly payments should be fine.
Or, even just… One quarter.
Is that too much for you?
No, it's fine.
Let's go.
Sir?
Can I help you?
I'm looking for Primo Estrella.
Oh, that's him over there.
- Thank you.
- Sure thing.
Primo Estrella?
How can I help you, Ma'am?
Who's asking?
June. You can call me June.
Dadong, get me a pen.
Here, Sir.
And get me another beer.
- A cold one.
- Yes, Sir.
And another for our guest.
Sir.
Read the documents too,
if it's not too much trouble.
CERTIFICATE OF LIVE BIRTH
What did you say your name was?
June?
That's right. June.
June.
I've seen that document before.
I've seen many others like it.
People keep mistaking me for their father.
What did your mom tell you?
Actually, I'm adopted.
I've never known my birth mother.
But I hired someone to look into my past.
And they led me to this birth certificate.
That's your name.
Pardon me, Dear.
But I'm not the only
Primo Estrella in the world.
It's someone with the same name.
Pardon me as well.
But the signature on the photo
and the one on my birth certificate
look exactly the same.
You're right.
Rowena Magpayo…
So, you're Weng's kid.
So?
Did you find her, too?
Where is she now?
She's already passed.
She's been gone for a while.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
What about you?
You signed my birth certificate.
Which means you knew I was out there.
Why didn't you look for me?
June…
That was a different time.
And I was a different person.
Nothing I can say will satisfy you.
I didn't look for you.
But you found me.
We're both here…
Now what?
Do we start crying?
I'm in a band, too.
I'm tired of this.
You can work all you want.
But there's always something.
Even when you're sleeping,
the debts keep growing.
It's embarrasing.
Sometimes…
I just want to quit.
One last ditch effort.
It's like what the Japanese did.
"Death before dishonor."
Hello, Daddy?
Hello, baby Mikey.
How are you?
I'm all right, Daddy.
I miss you.
I miss you too, Baby.
I'll see you soon, okay?
Okay, Daddy.
Baby?
Baby, I want to say sorry.
Why?
Because I'm not a good father.
That's not true, Daddy.
You're the coolest.
I told all my classmates that
my Daddy was a famous singer.
And then, I showed them all your videos.
And then they said
they wanted to see you play.
I'm so proud of you, Daddy.
Really, Baby?
Baby, I promise on my next gig
you can invite your friends, okay?
I'll sing for all of you, I promise.
Really, Daddy?!
You know, Dad, I told my teacher that
when I grow up
I want to be a rockstar like my Daddy.
That…
That makes me so happy, Baby.
That makes me so happy.
I promise you, I'll teach you
everything I know, okay?
I love you.
I love you, Daddy.
I love you so much.
I'll see you tomorrow, Baby.
Okay, Daddy, bye!
Bye.
So?
Where have you been all night?
Didn't I put you in charge of the clients?
They waited for you all night.
It's embarrassing.
Dad, I never said I accepted that job.
June…
You got fired from your job
so I gave you one
because you needed it!
Yes, Dad.
But I don't want to work for you!
It's our company!
When I'm gone, everything goes to you!
People are counting on you!
Dad, did it ever occur to you
to ask me what I want to do?!
But why?
Why wouldn't you want this?!
This is how we've survived!
This puts food on the table!
This put you through school!
This is our life!
This is our family's life!
- This is our legacy--
- Dad, I've had enough!
Dad, I've had enough fighting.
You're always yelling at me.
Dad, I don't want this anymore.
I'm tired of this!
Can't you see that I'm
doing this all for you?
All of this is for you!
Dad, this is not what I want.
I have other plans for my life.
This is how the Chinese
have always done it!
But, I'm not Chinese.
What do you mean you're not Chinese?!
You're a Chua!
I'm not a Chua!
I'm adopted, remember?!
I'm not your real daughter.
Beautiful, beautiful
You act so cold but everything's burnable
Just let me hear you whine
I'll try to act surprised
When these ends meet
So right before you try to say
Another wish to find your way
There's nothing left to fear
Somewhere you'll maybe come to
Make something beautiful
And when it hurts so much
A touch just ain't that bearable
When nothing's right and
You don't think you're okay
I'm there
Beautiful, beautiful
You see, the sun is but another miracle
The warmth of your own smile
Is just enough to make my darkness leave
I have a daughter.
I fell in love and then I got knocked up…
abandoned…
Sis, are you okay?
My shift got extended and
I have to stay until closing.
Can you still handle it?
Do I have a choice? Of course I will.
I've got ton of bills to pay.
Considering that my child's
got special needs.
Hello?
Is that so? Okay.
I'll try to make it home early, okay?
I'll do my best but
you handle things for now.
I'll do whatever it takes for her.
Even if I have to do it alone.
June…
Oh, Reggie.
Same Boat.
It's like an… S.O.S.
Or a 911.
It's a code word in our band.
When someone declares "Isang Bangka",
it means someone in the band needs help.
We all have to help without hesitating.
Thank you.
Is it just us?
For now, yes.
Your dad is Primo Estrella?
That's so sick!
Yes, I know.
It's a good thing I got to meet him.
But he says he doesn't remember me.
Well…
I was born in his messier days.
That explains a lot.
Oh?
So I was the mess? Really?!
Which one of us is the stoner?
You prick.
We aren't in the same situation.
It's a bit different with
me and my daughter.
What do you mean?
I was there, then I was gone for a while.
I need to make up for lost time.
Your daughter is still young
you'll have more than enough time.
I have an idea to do just that.
Let's get the band back together.
Let's do it. Just like the old days.
Are you up to it?
I just need my daughter to
see her dad in a better light.
How did you feel when you found out
your dad was a rockstar?
That's what I want my daughter to feel!
Fine.
But on one condition.
What?
You can't be like who you were.
You can't have a meltdown.
You can't do drugs.
You can't--
You're doing this for your daughter.
This is your second chance.
You can't give up.
Okay.
I'll hold you to that.
Don't make promises you can't keep.
June, when have I ever broken a promise?
Oh, Reggie you did.
You promised June that
you'd never leave her.
And then you did exactly that.
Thank you.
I'm done with promises. I--
I don't want to be letdown,
to gamble, to lose…
I don't want to…
get hurt.
I'm afraid of Reggie.
Do you still love him?
June…
Hi, Carla.
Same Boat.
What's wrong?
I sent something to all of you.
It's from Paola.
Okay, but why are you crying?
Just watch it. Please.
Okay, okay.
Hi, guys!
Welcome to my time machine.
If you're watching this,
that means…
I'm gone.
But, hold on.
You don't have to be so sad.
Think of it like I'm alive but
somewhere far away.
And this is how I want you to remember me.
THANK YOU - SINAGTALA
NEW SONG RELEASE - MARCH 11, 2012
Are you still here, Pao?
Can you hear me?
Damn it, Pao.
Everybody keeps leaving me.
You too?
Do you remember this?
This phone?
It's the same phone I had
when I ran away from home.
Then you called me.
You sang to me.
You told me to go back home.
And I listened to you Pao.
You're the only one I listened to.
If I sang to you now?
Will you come back home too?
I just need you to be strong
Don't be weary, this won't take long
Dear love…
Hold my hand be strong enough
Help is coming…
Don't worry I'm watching I won't…
Leave you behind
Here, sisig.
Reggie has something to say.
Some other time. It's nothing.
It's bad timing, is all.
What the--
Well, June opened it up.
Spit it out.
Don't keep us all in suspense.
I want to get the band back together.
How?
Paola's gone.
I don't want this.
I can't do it. Not without Paola.
You can do it yourselves.
But you'll have to replace me.
Me too.
Find someone else to take my place.
Well, if you're not in it,
then it's not Sinagtala.
Exactly my point.
Without Paola, it's not Sinagtala.
June?
I believe that
Pao would've wanted us
to continue with the band.
The reason I want the band back
is that we're happier
when we play together.
I feel the same way, too.
I still can't imagine that Pao's gone.
But I wouldn't ever want to play
without you guys.
I know it's bad timing.
But at least think about it.
Cheers, guys.
To Paola.
I'm done talking about my condition.
Because it's too late.
My journey's over.
I want to talk about you guys.
Let me ask you this:
What's your purpose in life?
I believe we're all here for a reason.
I know that because…
I love you, guys.
Find your purpose in life.
Individually, or together.
That's your reason to keep living.
June, you don't have to do that.
But I actually enjoy this.
Wow, thank you.
I heard something about a reunion.
Don't count on it.
Losing a bandmate is too painful.
That's how all bands are, June.
People come and go.
They don't always die, but…
Some people leave
or someone new comes along.
And sometimes,
a different band altogether.
My band was no different.
We had someone die, too.
What happened?
This guy,
his name's Nacho.
He was the best…
and we were in our prime.
But that's when it ended.
He died very young.
He killed himself?
He did.
There was nothing I could do.
Is it hard?
Is it hard to keep on going
even though you've lost one?
Songs are--
memories of the ones who wrote them.
Their spirit remains.
And when these songs are played
by the people who survive them…
Then the love between them lives on.
For what?
And for how long?
Don't you get tired of
playing the same old songs?
Well actually,
we made a new song.
But if you made a new song,
what does it have to do with Nacho?
He said he couldn't jump off that cliff
so he'll wait for a strong
wind to push him off.
We thought we'd make a song
that could stop that wind.
We wanted to become…
the wind that pushes people back.
Nacho was the reason for that song.
So,
he lives on through it.
Like a wind that pushes people back.
I don't know when the Lord will take me.
When I go to bed at night
then wake up in the morning,
that means my time isn't up yet.
But knowing it could be any day now,
everytime I wake up
is a reason to be grateful.
So, I try to be productive every day.
And today…
I'm busking!
Let's go.
Beautiful, beautiful
Won't you say if everything's horrible?
I like to see you smile
A different shade of light
In summer's heat
Take the shot!
- He made a pass!
- Oh, come on!
He moves like a queer, see?
He's soft as a baby.
Why don't you go cook my favorite,
the one you cook with chicken.
- Yes, let's get something to eat.
- Go cook something.
I just mentioned a wet noodle
and it went to your stomach.
- Hey.
- It's over. They lost again.
- Dad?
- Hmm?
Do you hate gay people?
Of course not, Son.
It was just an expression…
I meant he was soft and--
You can't be a player and move like that.
He moves queer. That's all I meant.
But it feels unfair to call him queer.
It's unfair to him
and to all queer people.
Son…
There's nobody gay in this house.
Who am I offending?
We're all guys here.
And don't worry about it.
I'm just old school.
It's just an expression.
"You're gay." "He's queer."
That's all it is. It means nothing.
They're just expressions. Don't worry.
But what if…
I were gay.
Would you still love me?
What're you talking about?
You got me good!
You almost had me!
If I didn't see you smiling,
I'd have believed you.
You almost scared me.
Jeez!
That's impossible knowing what I was.
You had me worried there.
There you go!
So, back to the question at hand.
What is your purpose?
If you don't know what it is yet,
that's okay!
Chill out.
Look inside yourselves.
And listen to your own voice.
Stop thinking about
what other people have to say.
What are the things that make you happy?
The things you're good at.
The things you enjoy
that give you a sense of fulfilment.
That's your purpose.
And the Lord gave you
those gifts and talents
to fulfill that purpose.
It can grow, but it can never change.
You cannot tell a seed
that it cannot be a tree.
That's what you call…
Destiny.
I know talking about the Lord
makes you guys uncomfortable.
But when you arrive at
the same place I have,
when you've seen and
felt everything I have…
You'll probably think of Him, too.
I'm telling you all something important,
so I hope you'll listen.
These talents we've been given
are too important to waste
on ourselves and other people.
They're for Him, too.
Our purpose isn't
just to make music that entertains people.
Can't there be a deeper reason?
When we were at our peak,
we wasted our gifts on the wrong thing.
We wasted them on personal goals.
And being rockstars went to our heads.
For a time,
we relied on ourselves so much
that we forgot about Him.
Maybe that's how we lost the band.
Because we didn't fulfill its purpose.
Why do you think music exists?
Why do you think we exist?
Isn't this all for Him?
So why don't we do everything…
for Him?
Make your life mean something.
And use it wisely.
Use it wisely.
Okay?
Have you thought about Pao's question yet?
What question?
About music…
And where it all comes from.
And why we play.
Have you?
Did you find your answer?
Not yet.
What about you? Do you have an answer?
Do you remember this?
Used to like the sound of the rain
And feel your arms around me
Together we go insane
But I wake up to where I should be
I've longed for the wind
They touch me through my feelings
And you'll never know till they begin
What you want is really what it means
Do you know why
we named the band "Sinagtala"?
Don't wanna be forever blue
'Cause I deserve some love that's true
Don't you think it's weird?
I never see the stars when we're together.
Maybe that means we aren't meant to be.
I don't think we need them, anyway.
You're my star light.
You're the brightest thing there is.
Cause I'm afraid, I'm afraid I'm afraid
To be forever blue
Gonna find some other guy for me
This time it will be just like the wind
Coming at the time it must be
And blowing to where I should be
I've longed for the wind
They touch me through my feelings
And you'll never know till they begin
What you want is really what it means
Don't wanna be forever blue
'Cause I deserve some love that's true
Finding it the hard way
And wishing for it every day
I guess I was wrong to want you, yeah
'Cause I'm afraid, I'm afraid, I'm afraid
To be forever blue
Don't wanna be alone
I need someone to hold on to
And share my dreams with a love, a love
That's always true
Don't wanna be forever blue
'Cause I deserve some love that's true
Finding it the hard way
And wishing for it every day
I guess I was wrong to want you, yeah
'Cause I'm afraid, I'm afraid, I'm afraid
To be forever
Blue
June.
Dad?!
Hello!
I need you to sign something for me.
- What are those, Dad?
- Oh, come here, dear.
- Some contract deals from our company.
- That's a lot.
I need you to sign these because
you're on the board of directors.
- But, it's so early.
- Yes.
Coffee?
It's so early in the morning.
Coffee in the morning.
Sugar?
- Uh, no. I'm fine.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Coffee. coffee.
Coffee for you.
It's only a few documents.
Do I have to read all of this?
No, it's fine. Do it later.
It can wait.
I'm not going to jail for this, am I?
If you go to jail, I'll have to go, too.
We'd be in prison together.
That would be fun.
Quite a lot already, huh.
Let's have breakfast.
They say these are the new ones.
CHING CHINESE CUISINE
Yum. Thank you.
June?
Go ahead, I'll have one too.
One for you.
Thank you.
Here.
Dad?
My fingers are hurting a little.
Could I just use a fork?
Sure, go on.
- Cheers.
- Cheers!
June.
I know you don't like
this business of ours.
But you're my only child.
And I'm doing this for you.
If I die,
and you decide to sell everything…
that'd be fine.
That'd be fine.
Do what you feel is right.
And stand by it.
I just want you to know…
that Daddy loves you very much.
But while I'm alive,
I still have things I want.
Come back to the company.
There's some thing I need you to handle.
I'm asking for your help.
Is it okay if I think about it?
That's okay.
Uhm.
Thank you.
For being… the best mom to Mikey.
Thanks for the patience
that you still have with me.
Thank you for…
thanks for loving me when you did.
Mara, it's just that…
I'm still trying to figure myself out.
I want to be a more responsible dad.
For me to be a better person.
And a better father to our child.
I just need a little more time.
And…
thank you.
That's all.
Wait.
Thank you.
Thank you for saying thank you.
Daddy!
If you ever feel lost, don't worry…
I do too.
I totally get the feeling
that our lives are worthless.
But that's when the Lord comes in.
He'll find you no matter
how far you've fallen.
He will rescue you from danger.
And he will provide everything you need.
Isko! Isko!
Your dad wants to see you.
- Where?
- Come on.
- Here he is.
- Boy Wonder!
Dad.
My son!
Do you know why you're here?
I have a gift for you.
A gift?
For what, Dad?
First, it's because you're the best son
anyone could ask for.
Second, I know law school's tough on you.
So, you need to relax.
Here.
Here's a keycard.
And this.
We'll wait for you downstairs.
We'll be there if you need us.
Carla?
Carr!
Carr, what are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
You should leave!
Open the door, Carr.
Leave.
Open the door.
I asked you to leave!
Carr!
So, you're a prostitute?
Who would hire you?
You have body odor.
I told you to leave.
Leave!
Carr!
What do you care?!
- Carr…
- Please just leave.
You could have told us you needed help.
Carr…
We're your friends.
You're my sissy, you know I love you.
Carr…
You should have told me.
Let's just tell them we're done.
That sounds gross.
Yuck.
Whore!
Fag!
You're a whore with body odor.
You're a fat fag.
Dad?
Son?
That was fast. What are you? A duck?
We're done.
Send her home.
Come on, Son.
That's brutal.
At least offer her a meal and a drink.
No, she'll be fine.
Nothing happened.
Isko,
is there something you aren't telling me?
Well, if…
nothing happened between the two of you,
I might as well make use of her.
Dad, let her go home.
Why would I do that?
I paid her a lot of money
and she won't have to do her job?
What kind of person are you, Dad?
Do you even know who she is?
She's like a sister to me!
If you paid any attention
to me in college,
you might have met her.
She's my bandmate.
Isko!
We know her better than you do!
Nicole is famous here!
Nicole isn't her name.
It's Carla.
Carla, a. k. a. Nicole!
Why are you so angry
about her selling herself?
Because she has needs!
And because there are people like you
who take advantage of people like her!
So please!
Let her go!
No!
I paid a lot of money for her,
and I didn't skimp on you!
But, Dad, I never needed this!
Because I'm gay!
I'm gay!
Isko!
Send her home!
I'm sick and tired of this life.
Paola?
The grip of darkness is pulling you under
Mightier than it's ever been before
The consolation is surrender
So you can't do this anymore
Your whole life is a choreograph
A basic circus act
You wear a costume and a mask
When really everything is black
Get up and fight the dark
And give it all you've got
Rise Above
So get up and fight the dark
And give it all you've got
Rise Above
Don't ignore the wounds from your past
Carla!
When off comes the guards and the cast
What's left is a battle scar
A reminder of how strong you are
So get up and fight the dark
And give it all you've got
RISE ABOVE - SINAGTALA LIVE PERFORMANCE
Rise Above
WOW! SO AMAZING
KEEP HEALING THE WORLD WITH YOUR VOICE
SINAGTALA OFFICIAL - 1.4M SUBSCRIBERS
She knows she can change the world
I know, I know, I know that she can change
I know I can change the world
Get up and fight the dark
And give it all you've got
Rise Above
So get up and fight the darkness
And give it all you've got
Rise Above
Come here, Pauline.
Nanny.
June…
- Hello.
- Say hi. Say hi.
- Say hi,
- Say hi, Auntie.
Send Tita a flying kiss.
Say hi. Kiss.
What's her name?
Pauline.
Hi, Pauline.
Nanny, you take care of her for a while.
How could you hide this from us?
Why did you not tell us?
You all have your own problems.
I didn't want to be a burden.
She's so beautiful.
She's so pure.
How could you even think
about leaving her?
Why does everyone want to end themselves?
Don't run away from your struggles.
We're always here for you.
I'm okay.
Stop, June, okay? Enough of your scolding.
Here. Come closer.
Stop selling yourself.
We're also Pauline's parents now.
From now on, I'm also Pauline's mother.
Isko and Reggie.
They're her fathers now, okay?
Isko is a mom, you know!
What are you talking about?
Dad?
Koy!
I'm gay.
I know.
You told me.
What about a one-on-one?
We'll bet on it.
What's on the line?
If I win,
you'll accept me as I am.
Okay.
But, if I win,
you'll have to marry
a woman of my choosing.
And…
you'll owe me a grandchild.
He's thinking…
You think you can fool me?
You got your smarts from me!
I call.
Wow, you call.
Okay.
Let's see who's ball it is.
Missed. It's my ball.
Yes, that's why you call it a miss.
I missed. Ha ha ha, I'm so funny.
How are you even gay?
You're so good at this.
There're plenty of gay players.
They just afraid to come out
because of people like you.
Oh wow, so it's my fault they're gay.
Gosh, kid.
Of all the things you
could have bet your life on,
you picked basketball.
Did you forget your dad was a pro?
Oops!
Three-One!
That means I'm up by…
Two.
What kind of girl do you want?
A fair one or a dark one?
An asian guy.
A tie!
I'm getting a grandchild!
And I'd like a baby girl.
Why'd you stop? Are you a sore loser?
It's not that!
Even if I win,
I'm leaving your house for good
if you're always going to
be talking shit about me!
It just hurts!
You?! You're hurt?
Don't you think I'm hurt, too?!
My only son,
my greatest treasure,
my pride and joy treats me this way!
Why, Dad?
Did anything even change?!
I'm still your son!
Your pride and joy!
Just because I came out
you don't love me anymore?!
Shut up!
Finish the game!
If you lose, you lose!
Do you think anything has changed?
You think I don't love you anymore
just because you're gay?
That's where you're wrong.
STAFF SUPPORT SERVICES
June, it's not looking good.
Hi, Mikey.
I'm your Tita June. Do you remember me?
Tita June, will you pray with me?
While we prayed,
I asked Paola, too.
I said to her…
"Pao…"
"If you're here, if you can hear us…"
"Take care of Reggie."
"You ask God for us. Tell him…"
"To forgive that stubborn fool."
"Because his daughter needs him."
At the hospital,
something happened that
I didn't tell the band about.
I saw Paola.
She had--
She had someone with her
but I couldn't see who it was.
But I knew somehow…
God was with her.
They asked me
what I wanted to do with my life.
I said…
That I wanted to spend it
with my daughter.
To be honest, I should be gone by now.
I wanted to run away from everything.
The struggles…
The shame…
The responsibility…
Life…
But I heard Paola's song again.
It was even trending online.
That's when I realized
that it wasn't just me.
"What is music for?"
What is music for?
Music exists
to remind us that we're not alone.
When I'm playing my guitar…
there are no more questions.
There's no judgement.
I am loved.
And through my music,
I love them back.
Where does music come from?
From a place of love.
Primo's bandmate said,
that he wouldn't jump off the cliff.
That he'd wait for the wind
to push him off.
Then Paola asked us.
What--
What is music for?
Why do we play music?
My answer, is Primo's answer.
Music is the wind that pushes back.
To save people from the cliff.
I know that you may feel broken.
I was too when I found out I was sick.
But even feeling broken has a purpose.
That's how the Lord tells
you to take a time-out.
"Chill out and listen to me."
Because we all make mistakes.
We take a fall down the wrong path.
But the Lord cares enough
to guide us back to him.
To the right path.
Like I said,
"You cannot tell a seed
that it cannot become a tree."
"But a seed has to die,
in order to become that tree."
We have been broken
to fulfill our destiny.
Amazing, isn't it?
Guys, we're about to start.
Let's pray?
- Yes?
- Yes.
Okay, let's pray.
Father in heaven…
guide our hands and our hearts
that we may play music well together.
Thank you, Lord, for the gift of music
and the opportunity to perform.
May our talents bring glory to your name.
This we ask, through Jesus Christ.
- Amen.
- Amen!
We live and die like a sunrise
We learn to breathe and we fade away
I'll never know, I'll never know
I'll never know if I'll die today
We're sick of trying
To live in these lives
We search for joy just to justify
I'll never know, I'll never know
I'll never know how to say goodbye
I just need you to be strong
Don't be weary this won't take long
Dear love, dear love
Hold my hand and don't give up
Help is coming, don't worry I'm watching
I won't leave you behind
Dear love, dear love
Trust me now, be strong enough
Help is coming, don't worry, I'm watching
I won't leave you behind
I just need you to be strong
Don't be weary, this won't take long
Dear love, dear love
Hold my hand and don't give up
Help is coming, don't worry, I'm watching
I won't leave you behind
Dear love, dear love
Trust me now, be strong enough
Help is coming, don't worry, I'm watching
I won't leave you behind
Dear love, dear love
Hold my hand and don't give up
Help is coming, don't worry, I'm watching
I won't leave you behind
Dear love, dear love
Trust me now, be strong enough
Help is coming, don't worry, I'm watching
I won't leave you behind
Sinagtala.
My band.
My family.
Same Boat.
Parang kahapon lang
Ang aking mundo
Umiikot para sa 'kin
Ako ang hari nito
Wala nang ibang nasa isip
Kundi ang pansarili lang
Sana noon pa'y nakita ko
Ikaw lang ang kailangan
Pakinggan mo
Tibok ng puso ko'y
Para sayo
Pagkat ikaw ang totoo
Nilinaw ng luha
Ang aking paningin
Sa wakas nasilayan ka
Pati ang ating damdamin
Marami pa tayong pagdadaanan
Dito ka lang
Sa aking tabi
Lahat ay makakayanan
Pakinggan mo
Tibok ng puso ko'y
Para sayo
Pagkat ikaw ang totoo
Pakinggan mo
Tibok ng puso ko'y
Para sayo
Pagkat ikaw lang ang
Ikaw ang totoo
Congratulations!
Carla!
That was amazing!
Yes!
Guys, Paola had another thing to say.
We're not done yet.
We have a long way to go.